## **DYMOND HOFFMAN**

LinkedIn

Springfield, Oregon | Phone: 541-972-6832 | Email: <a href="mailto:dymond.hoffman03@gmail.com">dymond.hoffman03@gmail.com</a>

## **Summary:**

Systematic Administrative Assistant with successful experience in fast-paced office settings. Hardworking team player with expertise completing various clerical tasks and offering staff support. Responsible, punctual, and productive professional when working with little to no supervision.

# Professional Experience Target - Springfield, OR

*Style Consultant* 4/2022 - 11/2022

- Maintained a positive attitude and extensive knowledge of product inventory and company procedure to handle guest inquiries
- Followed visual guidelines when adding merchandise to sales floor, setting display fixtures, and zoning floor pads
- Trained new hires
- Assisted as a backup cashier, performing all checkout procedures quickly and accurately
- Recognized as 'Team Member of the Month' for October 2022

# Wayfair - Springfield, OR

SSC - Customer Service Representative

3/2022

- Service customers with post order issues in an efficient manner via phone and email
- Navigate multiple software applications and technologies simultaneously
- Use de-escalation tactics and maintain a professional composure at all times
- Communicate with customers in a friendly manner and build a rapport with them, exceeding customer satisfaction

#### Gordon, Aylwoth & Tami, P.C - Eugene, OR

Administrative Assistant

7/2021 - 11/2021

- Handled finalizing legal document using adobe acrobat
- Meticulously reviewed and prepared documents for mailing
- Organized and filed court documents
- Operated postage machines, label makers, folding machines, printers, and scanners
- Improved productivity by consistently keeping folders cleared and managing the high volume of documents efficiently

### **Volunteer Experience**

# Springfield High School's Black Student Union - Springfield, OR

BSU Member 1/2021 - 7/2021

• Corresponded with administrators and staff to create a culturally inclusive school environment that represents all students of color

2 /2 /2 2

- Collaborated with students and staff to design and implement advisory lessons centered around systemic racism
- Provided resources and consultation for 15-minute advisory lessons taught by teachers schoolwide
- Increased the power of student voice and influenced the decision of including students of color to be a part of the interview committee for Springfield School District's first-ever Equity and Inclusion Coordinator
- Sparked a significant change in the school's culture and prompted several school-wide initiatives focused on equity, inclusion, and anti-racism

#### **Education**

High School Diploma, Springfield High School - Springfield, OR

- Notable achievements: Honor Roll, Graduated a year early with an unweighted GPA of 4.0
- **Relevant coursework:** Computer Applications, Spanish 1&2, Pre-Calculus, AP Literature and Composition

#### **Technical Skills**

**Office:** Google Suite, MS Office, Adobe Acrobat **Programming:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL